TOLU SMITH

Software Developer

Ibadan, Oyo State Nigeria | +234-80920-00376 | smyxbrone@gmail.com

CAREER SUMMARY:

a software developer more vested in backend development with strong analytical skills and proficiency in mathematics, solution-oriented, and problem solver with years of experience building and maintaining software and software architecture. Highly skilled in communication, collaboration, and technical documentation.

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Talos Africa (NodeJS, NestJs, Typescript, RPC, Web3Js, Solidity, RPC, Redis ,Docker etc.)

Web3 Developer | December, 2020 - May 2022

Figo Payment (JavaScript, NodeJS, NextJs, Redis, Docker etc.)

Backend Developer | March, 2021 - November, 2022

Paysure Solutions Ltd (NodeJS, Typescript, AWS, MariaDB etc.)

Contract Developer | April 2022 - Present

Smitiv Mobile Technology (NodeJS, Django REST, JavaScript, SQL, Linux, Docker etc.)

Backend Developer | May 2022 - Present

RELEVANT PROJECTS:

Hobbyist

Backend Developer | May, 2022 - July, 2022

• intended for collectors who want to inventory and understand the value of their collection over time

Food Hutz

Frontend Developer | 22 December, 2021 - April 2022

Home-made and local food delivery in the united kingdom

EDUCATION:

2015 - 2020 | University of ilorin

Bachelor of Engineering - Electrical & Electronics Engineering

SKILLS:

- Full stack web development
- Blockchain Technology
- Linux Systems
- Technical Analysis

STACKS

- Nodejs, NestJs and NextJs
- Solidity, Web3.js, and Web3.py
- Python, Diango
- AWS and Azure
- ReactJs, Docker ...